[
  {
  	"Question" : "Scale up to find a fraction equivalent to 2/5 with the denominator 20.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Scale up to find a fraction equivalent to two-fifths with the denominator 20.",
  	"Type" : "Scaling Up",
  	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
  	"Format" : "fraction",
  	"Answer" :
  	{
         "Numerator" : 8,
  		 "Denominator" : 20
  	},
  	"Hints" :
  	{
  	     "Hint1" : "For example, 1/2 can scale up to the fraction 2/4.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, one-half can scale up to the fraction two-fourths.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to find an equivalent fraction, you need to multiply the numerator and denominator by the same number.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to find an equivalent fraction, you need to multiply the numerator and denominator by the same number.",
         "Hint3" : "Try multiplying the numerator and denominator of 2/5 by 4.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "Try multiplying the numerator and denominator of two-fifths by 4."
  	},
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eight-twentieths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "In this problem, you multiply the numerator 2 and the denominator 5 of the fraction by 4 to get the equivalent fraction, which gives you the answer.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "In this problem, you multiply the numerator 2 and the denominator 5 of the fraction by 4 to get the equivalent fraction, which gives you the answer."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Scale up to find a fraction equivalent to 3/11 with the denominator 99.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Scale up to find a fraction equivalent to three-elevenths with the denominator 99.",
    "Type" : "Scaling Up",
    "Difficulty Level" : 2,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 27,
         "Denominator" : 99
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 1/4 can scale up to the fraction 3/12.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, one-fourth can scale up to the fraction three-twelfths.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to find an equivalent fraction, you need to multiply the numerator and denominator by the same number.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to find an equivalent fraction, you need to multiply the numerator and denominator by the same number.",
         "Hint3" : "Try multiplying the numerator and denominator of 3/11 by 9.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "Try multiplying the numerator and denominator of three-elevenths by 9."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-seven-ninety-ninths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "For this problem, you multiply the numerator 3 and the denominator 11 of the fraction by 9 to get the equivalent fraction, which gives you the answer.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "For this problem, you multiply the numerator 3 and the denominator 11 of the fraction by 9 to get the equivalent fraction, which gives you the answer."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Scale down to find the simplest fraction equivalent to 10/25.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Scale down to find the simplest fraction equivalent to ten-twenty-fifths.",
    "Type" : "Scaling Down",
    "Difficulty Level" : 1,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 2,
         "Denominator" : 5
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 2/6 can scale down to the simplest fraction 1/3.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, two-sixths can scale down to the simplest fraction one-third.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to find the simplest fraction, you need to divide the numerator and denominator by the same number.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to find the simplest fraction, you need to divide the numerator and denominator by the same number.",
         "Hint3" : "Try dividing the numerator and denominator of 10/25 by 5.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "Try dividing the numerator and denominator of ten-twenty-fifths by 5."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is two-fifths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "In this problem, you divide the numerator 10 and the denominator 25 each by 5. This gives you the simplest fraction.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "In this problem, you divide the numerator 10 and the denominator 25 each by 5. This gives you the simplest fraction."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Scale down to find the simplest fraction equivalent to 36/81.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Scale down to find the simplest fraction equivalent to thirty-six-eighty-firsts.",
    "Type" : "Scaling Down",
    "Difficulty Level" : 2,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 4,
         "Denominator" : 9
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 5/10 can scale down to the simplest fraction 1/2.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, five-tenths can scale down to the simplest fraction one-half.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to find the simplest fraction, you need to divide the numerator and denominator by the same number.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to find the simplest fraction, you need to divide the numerator and denominator by the same number.",
         "Hint3" : "Try dividing the numerator and denominator of 36/81 by 9.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "Try dividing the numerator and denominator of thirty-six-eighty-firsts by 9."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is four-ninths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "To do this problem, you divide the numerator 36 and the denominator 81 each by 9. This gives you the simplest fraction.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "To do this problem, you divide the numerator 36 and the denominator 81 each by 9. This gives you the simplest fraction."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Find the least common denominator of 5/7 and 3/4.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Find the least common denominator of five-sevenths and three-fourths.",
    "Type" : "Common Denominator",
    "Difficulty Level" : 1,
    "Format" : "value",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Value" : 28
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, the common denominator of 1/2 and 1/4 is 8.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, the common denominator of one-half and one-fourth is 8.",
         "Hint2" : "You need to find the smallest number that is a multiple of both denominators.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "You need to find the smallest number that is a multiple of both denominators.",
         "Hint3" : "Try listing out the multiples of the denominators. The multiples of 7 are 7, 14, 21, ... and the multiples of 4 are 4, 8, 12, ... Where do the two lists match up?",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "Try listing out the multiples of the denominators. The multiples of 7 are 7, 14, 21, and so on, and the multiples of 4 are 4, 8, 12, and so on. Where do the two lists match up?"
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is 28.",
    "Written Explanation" : "When you list the multiples of the denominators, 7 and 4, the two lists first match up at the number 28, meaning that this is the least common denominator of the two fractions.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "When you list the multiples of the denominators, 7 and 4, the two lists first match up at the number 28, meaning that this is the least common denominator of the two fractions."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Find the least common denominator of 17/10 and 3 1/25.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Find the least common denominator of seventeen-tenths and three and one-twenty-fifth.",
    "Type" : "Common Denominator",
    "Difficulty Level" : 3,
    "Format" : "value",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Value" : 50
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, the common denominator of 1/2 and 1/4 is 4.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, the common denominator of one-half and one-fourth is 4.",
         "Hint2" : "You need to find the smallest number that is a multiple of both denominators. Do not worry about the numerators or the whole number.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "You need to find the smallest number that is a multiple of both denominators. Do not worry about the numerators or the whole number.",
         "Hint3" : "Try listing out the multiples of the denominators. The multiples of 10 are 10, 20, 30, ... and the multiples of 25 are 25, 50, 75, ... Where do the two lists match up?",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "Try listing out the multiples of the denominators. The multiples of 10 are 10, 20, 30, and so on, and the multiples of 25 are 25, 50, 75, and so on. Where do the two lists match up?"
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is 50.",
    "Written Explanation" : "When you list the multiples of the denominators, 10 and 25, the two lists first match up at the number 50, meaning that this is the least common denominator of the two fractions.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "When you list the multiples of the denominators, 10 and 25, the two lists first match up at the number 50, meaning that this is the least common denominator of the two fractions."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Convert the mixed number 5 1/2 to an improper fraction.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Convert the mixed number five and one-half to an improper fraction.",
    "Type" : "Conversion",
    "Difficulty Level" : 1,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 11,
         "Denominator" : 2
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 1 1/3 can be converted to the improper fraction 4/3.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, one and one-third can be converted to the improper fraction four-thirds.",
         "Hint2" : "The first step is to multiply the denominator by the whole number. What should you do next?",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "The first step is to multiply the denominator by the whole number. What should you do next?",
         "Hint3" : "After multiplying the denominator and whole number, add that to the numerator.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "After multiplying the denominator and whole number, add that to the numerator."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eleven-halves.",
    "Written Explanation" : "For this problem, you first multiply the denominator 2 by the whole number 5 and add this to the numerator 1. 2 times 5 plus 1 is 11. The denominator stays the same.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "For this problem, you first multiply the denominator 2 by the whole number 5 and add this to the numerator 1. 2 times 5 plus 1 is 11. The denominator stays the same."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Convert the mixed number 6 3/5 to an improper fraction.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Convert the mixed number six and three-fifths to an improper fraction.",
    "Type" : "Conversion",
    "Difficulty Level" : 2,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 33,
         "Denominator" : 5
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 2 1/2 can be converted to the improper fraction 5/2.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, two and one-half can be converted to the improper fraction five-halves.",
         "Hint2" : "The first step is to multiply the denominator by the whole number. What should you do next?",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "The first step is to multiply the denominator by the whole number. What should you do next?",
         "Hint3" : "After multiplying the denominator and whole number, add that to the numerator.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "After multiplying the denominator and whole number, add that to the numerator."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-three-fifths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "For this problem, you first multiply the denominator 5 by the whole number 6 and then add this to the numerator 3. 5 times 6 plus 3 is 33. The denominator stays the same.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "For this problem, you first multiply the denominator 5 by the whole number 6 and then add this to the numerator 3. 5 times 6 plus 3 is 33. The denominator stays the same."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Convert the mixed number 12 1/4 to an improper fraction.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Convert the mixed number twelve and one-fourth to an improper fraction.",
    "Type" : "Conversion",
    "Difficulty Level" : 3,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 49,
         "Denominator" : 4
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 1 1/5 can be converted to the improper fraction 6/5.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, one and one-fifth can be converted to the improper fraction six-fifths.",
         "Hint2" : "The first step is to multiply the denominator by the whole number. What should you do next?",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "The first step is to multiply the denominator by the whole number. What should you do next?",
         "Hint3" : "After multiplying the denominator and whole number, add that to the numerator.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "After multiplying the denominator and whole number, add that to the numerator."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-nine-fourths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "First, you multiply the denominator 4 by the whole number 12 and then add this to the numerator 1. 4 times 12 plus 1 is 49. The denominator stays the same.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "First, you multiply the denominator 4 by the whole number 12 and then add this to the numerator 1. 4 times 12 plus 1 is 49. The denominator stays the same."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "In Charlie's closet, 1/5 of the clothes are black and 3/5 of the clothes are white. What fraction of the clothes are either black of white?",
    "Spoken Question" : "In Charlie's closet, one-fifth of the clothes are black and three-fifths of the clothes are white. What fraction of the clothes are either black or white?",
    "Type" : "Adding Like Denominators",
    "Difficulty Level" : 2,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 4,
         "Denominator" : 5
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 2/8 + 5/8 = 7/8.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, two-eighths plus five-eighths equals seven-eighths.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to add two fractions, should you add the numerators or the denominators?",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to add two fractions, should you add the numerators or the denominators?",
         "Hint3" : "Add the numerators of the two fractions. Remember, the denominator shouldn't change.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "Add the numerators of the two fractions. Remember, the denominator shouldn't change."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is four-fifths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "This is an addition problem, because we want to know the total fraction of clothes. Since the two fractions have the same denominator, you need to add the numerators 1 and 3, and keep the denominator 5 the same, to get the answer.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "This is an addition problem, because we want to know the total fraction of clothes. Since the two fractions have the same denominator, you need to add the numerators 1 and 3, and keep the denominator 5 the same, to get the answer."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "16/24 - 11/24 = ",
    "Spoken Question" : "What is sixteen-twenty-fourths minus eleven-twenty-fourths?",
    "Type" : "Subtracting Like Denominators",
    "Difficulty Level" : 2,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 5,
         "Denominator" : 24
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 3/4 - 2/4 = 1/4.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, three-fourths minus two-fourths equals one-fourth.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to subtract two fractions, should you subtract the numerators or the denominators?",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to subtract two fractions, should you subtract the numerators or the denominators?",
         "Hint3" : "Subtract the numerators of the two fractions. Remember, the denominator shouldn't change.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "Subtract the numerators of the two fractions. Remember, the denominator shouldn't change."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is five-twenty-fourths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "The two fractions have the same denominator, so you need to subtract the numerators, 16 and 11, and keep the denominator 24 the same.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "The two fractions have the same denominator, so you need to subtract the numerators, 16 and 11, and keep the denominator 24 the same."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "2/7 + 1/6 = ",
    "Spoken Question" : "What is two-sevenths plus one-sixth?",
    "Type" : "Adding Unlike Denominators",
    "Difficulty Level" : 2,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 19,
         "Denominator" : 42
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 1/2 + 1/3 = 5/6.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, one-half plus one-third equals five-sixths.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to add two fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to add two fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator.",
         "Hint3" : "The common denominator of the two fractions is 42. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Then you can add them!",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "The common denominator of the two fractions is 42. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Then you can add them!"
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nineteen-forty-secondths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "In this problem, the two fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 42. 2/7 can be written as 12/42, and 1/6 can be written as 7/42. Then, 12/42 + 7/42 gives you the answer.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "In this problem, the two fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 42. Two-sevenths can be written as twelve-forty-secondths, and one-sixth can be written as seven-forty-secondths. Then, twelve-forty-secondths plus seven-forty-secondths gives you the answer."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "3/8 + 1/4 + 3/5 = 
    Leave your answer as an improper fraction, and write your answer in lowest terms.",
    "Spoken Question" : "What is three-eighths plus one-fourth plus three-fifths? Leave your answer as an improper fraction, and write your answer in lowest terms.",
    "Type" : "Adding Unlike Denominators",
    "Difficulty Level" : 3,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 49,
         "Denominator" : 40
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 2/3 + 1/4 = 11/12.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, two-thirds plus one-fourth equals eleven-twelfths.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to add fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to add fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator.",
         "Hint3" : "The common denominator of the three fractions is 40. Now make the fractions have the same denominator. Then you can add them!",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "The common denominator of the three fractions is 40. Now make the fractions have the same denominator. Then you can add them!"
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-nine-fortieths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "In this problem, the three fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 40. 3/8 can be written as 15/40, 1/4 can be written as 10/40, and 3/5 can be written as 24/40. Then, 15/40 + 10/40 + 24/40 gives you the answer.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "In this problem, the three fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 40. Three-eighths can be written as fifteen-fortieths, one-fourth can be written as ten-fortieths, and three-fifths can be written as twenty-four-fourtieths. Then, fifteen-fortieths plus ten-fortieths plus twenty-four-fourtieths gives you the answer."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "7/4 - 1/9 = 
    Leave your answer as an improper fraction.",
    "Spoken Question" : "What is seven-fourths minus one-ninth? Leave your answer as an improper fraction.",
    "Type" : "Subtracting Unlike Denominators",
    "Difficulty Level" : 2,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 59,
         "Denominator" : 36
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 1/2 - 1/3 = 1/6.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, one-half minus one-third equals one-sixth.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to subtract two fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to subtract two fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator.",
         "Hint3" : "The common denominator of the two fractions is 36. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Then you can subtract them!",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "The common denominator of the two fractions is 36. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Then you can subtract them!"
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-nine-thirty-sixths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "The two fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 36. 7/4 can be written as 63/36, and 1/9 can be written as 4/36. Then, 63/36 - 4/36 gives you the answer.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "The two fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 36. Seven-fourths can be written as sixty-three-thirty-sixths, and one-ninth can be written as four-thirty-sixths. Then, sixty-three-thirty-sixths minus four-thirty-sixths gives you the answer."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "A movie is 9/5 hours long, and a baseball game is 13/6 hours long. How much longer is the baseball game than the movie?",
    "Spoken Question" : "A movie is nine-fifths hours long, and a baseball game is thirteen-sixths hours long. How much longer is the baseball game than the movie?",
    "Type" : "Subtracting Unlike Denominators",
    "Difficulty Level" : 3,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 11,
         "Denominator" : 30
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 2/3 - 1/4 = 5/12.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, two-thirds minus one-fourth equals five-twelfths.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to subtract two fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to subtract two fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator.",
         "Hint3" : "The common denominator of the two fractions is 30. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Then you can subtract them!",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "The common denominator of the two fractions is 30. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Then you can subtract them!"
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eleven-thirtieths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "This is a subtraction problem, because we want to know how much longer the baseball game is. The two fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 30. 13/6 can be written as 65/30, and 9/5 can be written as 54/30. Then, 65/30 - 54/30 gives you the answer.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "This is a subtraction problem, because we want to know how much longer the baseball game is. The two fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 30. Thirteen-sixths can be written as sixty-five-thirtieths, and nine-fifths can be written as fifty-four-thirtieths. Then, sixty-five-thirtieths minus fifty-four-thirtieths gives you the answer."
  }
]